Office for Campus Life Records UA219
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Campus Life Records
2010 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Campus Life
UA219
0.75 Linear Feet 2 boxes
39 Digital Object(s) 39 digital objects comprising 384 files.
1.12 Gigabytes
This collection contains publications, ephemera, photographs, fliers, posters and memos produced by the Office for Campus Life.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series: Ephemera, Publications, and 2021 accessions.
Biographical / Historical
Responsibility for new student orientation once fell under the pervue of the Orientation Committee. Currently, the Office for Campus Life takes a leadership role in the planning and implementation of New Student Orientation.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains publications, ephemera, photographs, fliers, posters and memos produced by the Office for Campus Life. Photographs, fliers, and posters document events organized by the Office for Campus Life and Tufts University Social Collective (TUSC). Memos to student organization leaders address guidelines and policies, trainings, events, and support for student organizations, including changes and restrictions due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office for Campus Life, 2011-2021, accessions 2011.113, 2012.030, UA-2021-.
Student life; Student Affairs and Services; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations
- Ephemera, 2010; UA219.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains promotional materials and ephemera created by the Office for Campus Life.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged by type.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Elephant handle mug, 2010; UA219.001.001.00001 (Box Shared 49)
- Publications, UA219.000003
  - Student Resource Publications, 2011; UA219-001 (Box 1)
- 2021 accessions, 2017 -- 2021; UA219.000006; 1.12 Gigabytes; 39 Digital Object(s) 39 digital objects comprising 384 files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by John Wescott, Associate Director for Campus Life, Programming, February 2021, accession UA-2021-033.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  This bulk of this series consists of photographs, fliers, and posters from events organized by the Office for Campus Life and Tufts University Social Collective (TUSC). Many of these events, including 100 Days, Fall Fest, Fall Gala, Senior Week, Spring Fling, Tuftonia's Day, Welcome Back Seniors, and Winter Ball, occur annually. Also included in this series are memos sent to student organization leaders from the Office for Campus Life. These memos address guidelines and policies, trainings, events, and support for student organizations, including changes and restrictions due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
  - Fall Fest, 2017; UA219.000007; 27.59 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
  - Fall Gala, 2017; UA219.000008; 1.91 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Junior Sendoff, 2017; UA219.000009; 3.85 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
  - Parents Weekend, 2017; UA219.000010; 34.4 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 15 files.
  - Spring Fling, 2017; UA219.000011; 40.7 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
  - Student Organization Fair, 2017; UA219.000012; 20.25 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
  - Welcome Back Seniors, 2017; UA219.000013; 38.61 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 12 files.
  - 100 Days, 2018; UA219.000014; 7.16 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
  - Baccalaureate, 2018; UA219.000015; 35.94 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 13 files.
  - Commencement, 2018; UA219.000016; 7.96 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
  - Escape Tisch, 2018; UA219.000017; 24.46 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.
  - Fall Fest, 2018; UA219.000018; 10.38 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
  - Fall Gala, 2018; UA219.000019; 26.27 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - Homecoming, 2018; UA219.000020; 37.74 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 15 files.
  - Senior Week, 2018; UA219.000021; 105.99 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 17 files.
  - Spring Fling, 2018; UA219.000022; 11.54 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
  - Student Organization Fair, 2018; UA219.000023; 28.92 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
  - Tuftonia's Day, 2018; UA219.000024; 7.8 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
  - Welcome Back Seniors, 2018; UA219.000025; 39.04 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 9 files.
  - Winter Ball, 2018; UA219.000026; 8.13 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - 100 Days, 2019; UA219.000027; 4.94 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 9 files.
  - Fall Gala, 2019; UA219.000028; 5.86 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - Halloweekend, 2019; UA219.000029; 61.33 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
  - Homecoming Concert, 2019; UA219.000030; 45.7 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
  - Roll Back the Stress, 2019; UA219.000031; 46.3 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Senior Series, 2019; UA219.000032; 91.16 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
  - Senior Week, 2019; UA219.000033; 34.69 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 16 files.
  - Spring Fling, 2019; UA219.000034; 18.18 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - Tuftonia's Day, 2019; UA219.000035; 16.64 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
  - Tufts Belly Dance, 2019; UA219.000036; 60.87 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
  - WW Candyland, 2019; UA219.000037; 40.39 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
  - Winter Ball, 2019; UA219.000038; 23.23 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - 100 Days, 2020; UA219.000039; 6.73 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 11 files.
  - Antoni, 2020; UA219.000040; 123.55 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.
  - Goat Yoga, 2020; UA219.000041; 7.06 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.
  - Tie-Dye, 2020; UA219.000042; 15.39 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Tisch Casino, 2020; UA219.000043; 12.34 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
  - Student organization memos, 2019 September -- 2021 January; UA219.000044; 16.97 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 31 files.